(Penny:)Yeah, I don't need
anything around
(Penny:)that I can stab myself with.
(Sheldon:)Wonderful,
(Sheldon:)Longclaw is mine.
(Sheldon:)And how about you keep
(Sheldon:)our... avocado plant?
(Leonard:)Sounds right--
a limited edition collectible
(Leonard:)worth hundreds of dollars
(Leonard:)and a thing
(Leonard:)that grew out of a thing
we fished from the trash.
(Sheldon:)Although, Amy and I did
just move in together,
(Sheldon:)and a plant is
a lovely housewarming gift.
(Leonard:)Fine, take the plant.
(Sheldon:)Oh, we got a sword
and a plant;
(Sheldon:)our apartment's
really shaping up.
(Bernadette:)Stuart, you didn't have
to get us a baby gift.
(Sheldon:)Oh.
(Stuart:)Just homemade coupons for things
you might need help with
(Stuart:)before the baby gets here.
(Stuart:)Going to the grocery store,
driving you to the doctor.
(Stuart:)If you're not in a hurry,
I can dig you a koi pond.
(Bernadette:)A foot massage?
(Stuart:)And that's not me being creepy,
that's for either of you.
(Howard:)This is very nice,
Stuart, thank you.